[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 31]
You were originally from the Mystic Panther Clan.
Someone used a secret technique
to suppress your beastly nature for nearly 10 years.
Suddenly breaking free from the restraints,
it's naturally difficult to control yourself.
If you can't control it,
then don't try to control it anymore.
Follow your bloodline.
Do what you want to do.
You are so powerful.
This world
should be your hunting ground.
It's you?
How about it?
Now you know
your true identity, don't you?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm just telling you the truth.
You don't hate those who kept it from you,
but you hate me instead?
You're really ungrateful.
None of your business.
You are my brother.
Of course this is my business.
I won't go with you.
Dream on!
You're so stubborn.
I'll beat some sense into you.
Xuanye!
If you have the guts, just kill me.
You'd rather die than be a demon.
What kind of
spell did they put you under
to make you so devoted?
I'll ask you one more time.
Are you coming with me or not?
Don't even think about it.
Fine.
Humans and demons can't coexist.
You're a demon,
yet you're desperate to be human.
Then I'll grant your wish.
I'll let you see
whether anyone will still accept you
if your identity is exposed.
Xuanye, are you alright?
Father,
Mother,
Big Brother,
I've come to see you again.
All these years,
whenever I return from demon hunting,
I always come to visit you,
clean your room,
and tell you
about my experiences
while hunting demons.
It's as if
you're right here beside me.
Father,
I never understood before
why
I couldn't remember
anything before I was 12,
why
you gave me the Peerless Bracelet,
you wouldn't let me go to the Underground City,
and why
all of you were poisoned by demons
while I alone was unaffected.
Now,
I understand everything.
It's actually quite simple.
Because
I am a demon.
♫Just sobered up after a dream, sighing for my life♫
A demon
♫In this desolate mortal world♫
who ended up as a demon hunter.
♫The other side sees fantasies fading into obscurity♫
How ironic.
♫Is it a blessing or a calamity?♫
♫I'm all alone♫
♫Braving the snowstorm♫
♫Struck by sudden amnesia♫
Father,
you once told me
♫Wait until the last peach blossom falls♫
♫Glance back with love for 10,000 years♫
that people can be good or evil,
and demons
are the same.
I can't generalize.
♫If there were no regrets♫
Only I can
♫Why would the starlight still remain♫
decide who I am.
♫To illuminate the world?♫
But now,
♫Coated in starlight, holding gleaming swords♫
who am I?
♫Before daybreak♫
Father,
♫May you have no regrets♫
♫Together, through seas and mountains♫
do you know?
♫If all must fade away and be forgotten♫
♫I'd keep it all to myself♫
♫If we luck out♫
I'm leaving.
♫Let's reunite once again beyond the time♫
I won't be coming back.
♫I'm all alone♫
♫Braving the snowstorm♫
♫Struck by sudden amnesia♫
♫Wait until the last peach blossom falls♫
♫Glance back with love for 10,000 years♫
♫If there were no regrets♫
♫Why would the starlight still remain♫
♫To illuminate the world?♫
♫Coated in starlight, holding gleaming swords♫
♫Before daybreak♫
How is she?
♫May you have no regrets♫
♫Together, through seas and mountains♫
The fever has gone down.
♫If all must fade away and be forgotten♫
♫I'd keep it all to myself♫
She's okay.
♫If we luck out♫
♫Let's reunite once again beyond the time♫
Come quickly!
Let's begin!
Come on, pass the ball!
Give it to me!
Xuanye,
will we ever return to Guangping?
I don't know.
Then where will we go?
Should we open a pharmacy somewhere else?
Xuanye,
if you have nowhere else to go,
why don't you come with me?
You taught me how to be human before
and you did a good job.
Now it's my turn to teach you how to be a demon.
Don't worry.
I'm sure I can teach you well.
If you're willing,
you could even be my companion demon.
Or I could be your companion demon.
I don't care about these things.
Chi Xue.
Don't follow me anymore.
Why?
When I transform,
my mind becomes chaotic.
I can't control myself.
I'm afraid I might hurt you.
It's okay.
I can run fast.
Next time, I'll run as soon as you transform.
I'll come back when you return to human form.
I promise you won't be able to catch me.
Xuanye,
don't be upset.
There's nothing wrong with being a demon.
Didn't your father say before
that humans and demons are the same?
As long as you act righteously,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
I'm a panther demon.
Aren't you afraid I'll eat you?
You are Xuanye.
Xuanye never eats rabbits.
Hurry!
Don't let that panther demon escape!
The demon is over there!
Quick, let's go!
Over there, hurry!
Hurry!
It's over there! Let's go, quick, quick, quick!
Hurry up!
They said panther demon.
Could it be...
Let's go check it out.
We've searched everywhere, inside and outside the city.
There's not
a single trace of Xuanye.
Banxia has left with her parents.
He'll be furious when he hears about this.
This guy...
Seriously...
He left without even
saying goodbye to us.
Wen Jian.
Who are those two?
They must be
the demon hunters the lord invited.
Demon hunters?
Hasn't Xuanye already gone?
Why do we need other demon hunters?
Xuanye was supposed to
get married recently, wasn't he?
You think the lord
is as shortsighted as you?
Bad news!
Chief Constable Chu,
Chief Constable Wen,
the panther demon...
The panther demon has appeared again!
The demonic aura is strong.
It must be in these mountains.
I can smell it too.
Where is it?
It's coming from you.
Let's split up and search.
Chi Xue.
Be careful.
Don't try to be a hero.
Got it!
Mother!
I want to go home!
I'm scared.
You're fast.
Demon!
Are you talking about yourself?
So fierce.
Very well.
Since you like to play,
I'll play with you.
Nine Spirits Suppression.
Reverse Blood Flow!
How's that?
Fun, isn't it?
This is the Heart-Killing Technique that Father taught me personally.
I never thought the first time
I'd use it would be on you.
How is it?
Compared to the techniques
your human father taught you,
which is
superior?
I've sealed your transformation ability.
For the time being,
don't even think about changing back to human form.
Man Ying,
don't hate me.
All my arrangements
were simply to teach you
why they say humans and demons walk different paths.
Time is short.
Understand it soon.
Over here!
You insolent demon,
you dared to enter the city
and hurt people in broad daylight.
The demon is injured.
Kill it!
Kill!
Demon, prepare to die!
Chi Xue!
How was that?
Am I impressive?
Run! I'll protect you.
Go!
Go...
Just a beast waiting for slaughter.
Everyone,
subdue the demon!
My Lady.
My Lady!
Banxia.
Banxia!
My Lady!
Banxia.
What's wrong, Banxia?
Did you have a nightmare?
Banxia.
Where are we?
We are
on our way back to our hometown in Nanyang.
Banxia.
Last night,
you were delirious with fever.
Your father was afraid that when you woke up,
you wouldn't want to leave.
So he made the decision early this morning
and we set off for home.
♫Melody echoes along the river; wild geese soar in sudden fright♫
Mother.
♫The music ends, and I stand in solitude♫
I can't leave.
Mother, I can't leave.
♫I see you turn into a handful of starlight♫
I know.
♫Drifting past me♫
I know Grandmother is getting old.
She needs me to go back and keep her company.
I should go back,
♫In tears, the past memories still glow♫
but Xuanye is now
in danger.
♫Crystallized into cold amber♫
I can't leave him alone.
♫I know it also brought you great pain to let go♫
I can't abandon him.
Banxia.
♫But why did you♫
But if you go back now,
what can you do?
♫Still endure the pain and shatter♫
I can stay with him.
I can comfort him.
If he's in danger,
♫Remember me, don't miss me♫
I can save him.
Mother,
you've been locked up before.
♫Don't put the blame on yourself for my solitude♫
You've been restrained by others.
♫I hate that I failed♫
You know it.
You definitely don't want to be abandoned
♫To catch the glistening starlight♫
and left behind,
right?
Mother,
please help me.
♫We were meant to miss each other in this life♫
I can't go.
♫Only after missing did we learn how much love could hurt♫
These fruits are good.
I will
bring some to Banxia.
♫To have loved you is to have truly lived♫
Alright.
Come on,
give me some.
Okay.
And this one too.
Let's go, let's go.
Tingzhou.
Is Banxia awake?
Not yet.
Banxia.
♫Remember me, don't miss me♫
♫Don't put the blame on yourself for my solitude♫
Tingzhou.
Where did she go?
♫I hate that I failed♫
♫To catch the glistening starlight♫
♫We were meant to miss each other in this life♫
♫Only after missing did we learn how much love could hurt♫
♫To have loved you is to have truly lived♫
Lord Geng.
Immortal Masters,
how should we
handle that beast?
This beast is a black panther demon.
This demon is fierce.
With just my disciple and I alone,
it's difficult to eliminate it.
However,
I have already informed my sect
and requested my master to handle it.
That's excellent.
Well,
I'll leave it to you two Immortal Masters to handle then.
Please,
don't let that demon suddenly attack and harm people again.
Please rest assured, Lord Geng.
With the two of us here,
it won't dare.
Thank you for your efforts.
Master,
this demon is quite fierce.
On the way back, I've already sent a letter
to that lord in the Underground City.
Once we receive the reward,
we'll hand it over.
This matter
will then have nothing to do with us.
Master,
haven't we seen
this demon somewhere before?
What do you mean?
Just a feeling.
Feeling?
Your cultivation is not sufficient.
Don't let your imagination run wild all day.
Focus on your cultivation.
[Ganshan Clinic]
What are you doing?
The lord said
it's the demon hunters' duty to exorcise demons
and protect the Way.
No one is allowed to give them trouble.
But...
If it weren't for those two.
Chi Xue wouldn't have died.
Chi Xue was a demon.
Do you want to seek justice
for a demon in the government office?
Even if you want to,
you must plan for the long term.
Besides, I always feel
something is off about this matter.
Why would Chi Xue be willing
to risk his own life
to help that panther demon?
Stop it! All of you, stop it!
What are you trying to do?
There's a demon locked up in here.
You're being way too reckless!
Demon?
So what if it's a demon?
It ate my child!
A life for a life!
I want it to pay with its life!
Right, make it pay with its life!
Fellow villagers!
Everyone, please calm down and listen to me.
The demon indeed deserves to die.
It's our responsibility as demon hunters
to eliminate evil demons
and protect the people.
However, this demon is fierce and dangerous.
Ordinary methods won't work against it.
You won't be able to kill it either.
Therefore,
we need to take it back to our sect
and let my master deal with it.
Nonsense!
How can it not be killed?
I don't care what kind of demon it is.
Today,
I'll burn it to death with fire!
You can't take the demon away!
We must burn it to death right here!
Stop making trouble!
Stop causing a commotion!
Oh, my son...
Burn it to death.
We must burn it to death today!
I'm 36 years old
and only had this one son,
but it ate him!
I don't care!
I want it to pay with its life!
The demon must pay with its life!
It's that one!
Fellow villagers,
this is the one that harmed my child!
I'll fight you to the death!
Kill it! Burn it to death!
All of you, stop!
Whoever causes more trouble
will be locked up!
Who let the villagers in?
Ask your own men
why they didn't stop the villagers
from barging in.
Why did you lower this black cloth?
The villagers have harbored too much resentment.
It's good to let them vent a little.
Who gave you the authority?
Lord Geng has already
entrusted me to manage this place.
Come with me to see Lord Geng.
Chief Constable Wen!
Banxia.
Any news about Xuanye and Chi Xue?
I just went to Ganshan Clinic,
but the door was still closed.
Have they returned?
I...
Did something happen?
This morning, a panther demon appeared
and abducted a child outside the academy.
Lord Geng
summoned two demon hunters.
For some reason,
Chi Xue desperately protected
that black panther demon.
He...
Chi Xue died?
Xuanye has also disappeared.
He probably doesn't know about this yet.
What about that panther demon?
Where is the panther demon?
It was captured by those two demon hunters.
It's locked up in the courtyard.
Demon!
Kill the demon! Demon!
Beat the demon! Kill it! Burn it!
Stop! Don't hit it anymore!
Stop smashing! Stop smashing!
Stop hitting it!
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I didn't tell you.
Tell me
how I can help you escape,
Xuanye.
Tell me quickly.
Tell me
how I can help you escape!
Kill it!
We can't let it live!
Run!
Banxia!
Banxia! Ban—
Get out of the way!
There's no one here anymore.
Xuanye, you...
Are you alright?
Don't be angry with me.
You think if you're mean to me,
you'll scare me away?
I've searched for you for so long.
I've thought about you for so long.
How could I possibly
be scared away so easily?
Run! Don't worry about me!
So what's your name?
My name is Man Ying!
Now, run!
I remember I told you before.
When I was little, I encountered danger.
A boy named Man Ying
saved me.
He was injured while saving me.
A drop of his blood fell
into my left eye.
Since then,
I've been able to see demons.
Everyone told me
that it was just a dream.
Only I knew
it wasn't.
But for some reason,
I could never find
that place again.
I couldn't find Man Ying anymore.
I thought that was the end.
If it was a dream,
one would eventually wake up.
Wouldn't I become crazy
if I lived in a dream forever?
Xuanye...
We've met again.
It's just that you don't remember
that you are Man Ying.
You don't remember me.
But I haven't forgotten.
What's wrong?
Xuanye!
Beast.
Attack!
You've made a mistake!
He's not the one who hurt people.
Banxia!
It's dangerous!
Come here quickly!
Don't hurt him! He's Xuanye!
Catch the panther demon.
Stop it!
Xuanye, I'm fine.
It's okay.
Miss Duan.
Immortal Master!
Xuanye.
Xuan...
Master,
he—
Mother!
Son!
Son, son!
You're back!
Let me see if you're hurt.
Mother.
It's alright.
There, there. Don't cry.
Good child, it's alright, it's alright.
It's good that you're back.
It's good you're back.
Don't cry now, it's okay, it's okay.
My Lord, why did you arrest Banxia?
She's not a demon.
That's right, My Lord.
Let me ask you all.
The two Immortal Masters said
that Xuanye is that black panther demon.
Is it true or false?
My Lord,
that's just
their one-sided statement.
Then where is Xuanye now?
Isn't Xuanye often away?
Maybe he's gone to catch demons.
But that rabbit demon
is his companion, right?
In that case,
that case from six years ago
must be related to him.
This case has wide implications.
Until it's fully investigated,
Duan Banxia
is not allowed to leave even half a step.
-My Lord.
You may all leave now.
Miss Duan,
we meet again.
You called that panther demon Xuanye.
Could is be that the successor of the Eight Pillar Sect
is a demon?
Even if you don't tell me,
I can still catch him.
Did anyone actually see that panther demon
abduct the child?
Yes,
it was witnessed.
That's impossible.
Xuanye would never harm anyone.
The one who abducted the child
must be another demon.
You've got the wrong person.
Masters,
the child has been returned.
Banxia is injured
and the lord refuses to release her.
I don't know if she can hold on
in prison.
Poor Banxia.
I just never thought
Xuanye was really a panther demon.
I've known Xuanye for so many years,
and have seen him catch so many demons with my own eyes.
I never expected this.
No wonder Chi Xue
protected him at all costs before.
It seems Banxia
has known Xuanye's identity all along.
So what if she knew?
The kidnapped child
has been released, hasn't he?
It proves it wasn't Xuanye.
But you should know
that to the people,
Xuanye will always be a demon.
What does it matter if one is a demon or human?
If demons don't harm and humans don't do evil,
neither should be arrested.
Why are you here?
To help, of course.
Help?
You don't need it?
We do.
Better late than never.
How can you help?
By rescuing Banxia.
I am a judicial commissioner of the Court of Judicial Review.
I have the authority to supervise, impeach, and review cases.
I believe this case of yours
has been misjudged.
So I want to bring out the detained suspect
for questioning
to review this case.
Your rank is lower than Lord Geng's.
How can you review it?
We'll review it secretly.
How secretly are we talking?
We'll quietly bring the person out.
What if someone tries to stop us?
Knock them out.
Isn't that a jailbreak?
No, jailbreaking is illegal.
This is just flexible case handling.
Well,
can we do it without knocking people out?
Sure.
You figure it out.
Xuanye.
Uncle.
Xuan...
Xuanye?
She's awake.
Go find Xuanye.
We need to go to
the Underground City's Sky Cavern
to find Xuanye.
I know,
but you're seriously injured right now.
Come on.
Rest for a while first.
We'll go tomorrow.
Uncle.
Xuanye.
You're awake.
How long have I been asleep?
You've been asleep for three days.
Here.
Three days?
Drink some water.
Come.
Banxia.
Don't worry.
My people reported that
Miss Duan
has already been rescued by your friends.
Rescued?
Yes.
Here.
Drink some water.
I've been busy taking care of you lately,
so I couldn't look after her.
Don't worry.
I've already sent people to find her.
Thank you, Uncle.
I've been keeping an eye on
the situation in Guangping.
I heard you were in trouble,
so I rushed over immediately.
But I didn't expect to be a step too late.
Xuanye,
your Peerless Bracelet
was shattered in the painted world
by the Moon-Fearing Demon.
Without the Peerless Bracelet,
you revealed your true form.
Uncle, you've known
my identity for a while, haven't you?
Yes,
but the Peerless Bracelet
is an extremely rare magic tool.
The method of its creation
was known only to your father.
So I...
It's just a clever illusion.
I don't want another one.
What?
Are you blaming your father?
Xuanye,
things are not
as you imagine them to be.
Your father has been
protecting you all along.